Ivy Society Publications UP016
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Ivy Society Publications
1895 -- 1977
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
Ivy Society
UP016
2.95 Linear Feet
3 Volumes
1 Artifact(s)
217 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Tufts Song Books; and The Ivy Book.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Ivy Book student handbook and the Tufts song books published by the Ivy Society beginning in 1895.
Biographical / Historical
The Ivy Society, originally known as Ivy Leaf, was the honor society for the junior class in Arts and Sciences. The Ivy Society was formulated to foster class spirit in the junior class as well as to do away with "factional feeling which may exist on the Hill," though these two goals were somewhat contradictory. For many years the Ivy Society's main activity was the preparation and production of the Ivy Book, a handbook for the college, which became an essential publication for incoming students from its first appearance in the 1902-03 academic year. It was an annual publication which ceased in 1971, when it was replaced first by a student handbook produced by the college, and then by the Pachyderm.
The duties assigned to the Ivy Society by the student council were to publish the Ivy Book, to run dances after basketball games, to have charge of Junior Day and Junior Prom, to run organized football trips, to act as ushers at formal Chapel functions, to look after athletic trophies, to gather together the pictures of the current athletic teams, and to conduct Senior and Freshman elections, including the counting of votes.
Election to the society at first was by vote of the faculty, but after the first class was elected, election was by the membership of the society, who selected the following year's members from the Junior class. During the academic year 1923-24, there was criticism as some felt that fraternity politics and popularity had undue weight in the selection process. A revision of the rules in 1929-30 changed the process and from that time forward the society nominated qualified members of the rising class, and the class as a whole voted to elect members of the society.
The last elections for the society were held in April 1969 for the 1969-70 academic year.
- Tufts Song Book, 1895 -- 1922; UP016.001; 0.75 Linear Feet; 3 Volumes; 1 Artifact(s); 217 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  A collection of music for and by alumni and students of Tufts University, published by the Ivy Society. Includes the Alma Mater, Hymn to College Hill, For Tufts Hurrah, The Brown and Blue, and other local and traditional favorites.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts Song Book, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
    Tufts Song-Book, edition of 1906. A publication of the Ivy Society.
    Music; Cheers; Tufts University; Ivy Society
    - Tufts Song Book, Cover, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
      image/tiff
    - Tufts Song Book, Title Page, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, Copyright Page, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, Dedication Page, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, v, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, vii, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, viii, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00007 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 1, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00008 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 2, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00009 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 3, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00010 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 4, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00011 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 5, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00012 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 6, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00013 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 7, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00014 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 8, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00015 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 9, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00016 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 10, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00017 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 11, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00018 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 12, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00019 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 13, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00020 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 14, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00021 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 15, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00022 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 16, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00023 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 17, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00024 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 18, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00025 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 19, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00026 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 20, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00027 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 21, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00028 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 22, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00029 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 23, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00030 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 24, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00031 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 25, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00032 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 26, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00033 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 27, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00034 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 28, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00035 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 29, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00036 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 30, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00037 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 31, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00038 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 32, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00039 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 33, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00040 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 34, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00041 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 35, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00042 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 36, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00043 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 37, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00044 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 38, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00045 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 39, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00046 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 40, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00047 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 41, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00048 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 42, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00049 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 43, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00050 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 44, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00051 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 45, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00052 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 46, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00053 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 47, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00054 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 48, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00055 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 49, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00056 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 50, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00057 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 51, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00058 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 52, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00059 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 53, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00060 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 54, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00061 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 55, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00062 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 56, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00063 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 57, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00064 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 58, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00065 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 59, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00066 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 60, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00067 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 61, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00068 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 62, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00069 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 63, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00070 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 64, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00071 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 65, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00072 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 66, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00073 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 67, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00074 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 68, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00075 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 69, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00076 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 70, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00077 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 71, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00078 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 72, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00079 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 73, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00080 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 74, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00081 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 75, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00082 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 76, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00083 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 77, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00084 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 78, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00085 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 79, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00086 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 80, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00087 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 81, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00088 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 82, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00089 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 83, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00090 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 84, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00091 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 85, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00092 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 86, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00093 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 87, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00094 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 88, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00095 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 89, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00096 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 90, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00097 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 91, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00098 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 92, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00099 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 93, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00100 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 94, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00101 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 95, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00102 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 96, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00103 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 97, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00104 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 98, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00105 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 99, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00106 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 100, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00107 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 101, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00108 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 102, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00109 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 103, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00110 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 104, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00111 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 105, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00112 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 106, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00113 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 107, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00114 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 108, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00115 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 109, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00116 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 110, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00117 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 111, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00118 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 112, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00119 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 113, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00120 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 114, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00121 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 115, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00122 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 116, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00123 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 117, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00124 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 118, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00125 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 119, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00126 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 120, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00127 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 121, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00128 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 122, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00129 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 123, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00130 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 124, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00131 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 125, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00132 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 126, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00133 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 127, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00134 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 128, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00135 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 129, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00136 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 130, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00137 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 131, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00138 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 132, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00139 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 133, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00140 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 134, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00141 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 135, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00142 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 136, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00143 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 137, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00144 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 138, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00145 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 139, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00146 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 140, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00147 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 141, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00148 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 142, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00149 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 143, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00150 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 144, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00151 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 145, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00152 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 146, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00153 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 147, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00154 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 148, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00155 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 149, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00156 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 150, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00157 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 151, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00158 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 152, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00159 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 153, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00160 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 154, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00161 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 155, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00162 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 156, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00163 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 157, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00164 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 158, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00165 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 159, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00166 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 160, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00167 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 161, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00168 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 162, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00169 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 163, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00170 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 164, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00171 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 165, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00172 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 166, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00173 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 167, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00174 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 168, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00175 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 169, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00176 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 170, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00177 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 171, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00178 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 172, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00179 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 173, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00180 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 174, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00181 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 175, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00182 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 176, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00183 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 177, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00184 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 178, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00185 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 179, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00186 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 180, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00187 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 181, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00188 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 182, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00189 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 183, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00190 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 184, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00191 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 185, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00192 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 186, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00193 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 187, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00194 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 188, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00195 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 189, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00196 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 190, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00197 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 191, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00198 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 192, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00199 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 193, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00200 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 194, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00201 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 195, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00202 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 196, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00203 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 197, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00204 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 198, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00205 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 199, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00206 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 200, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00207 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 201, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00208 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 202, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00209 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 203, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00210 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 204, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00211 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 205, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00212 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 206, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00213 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 207, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00214 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, page 208, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00215 (Box Volume 1)
    - Tufts Song Book, Back Cover, 1906; UP016.001.001.00001.00216 (Box Volume 1)
  - The Book of Tufts Music, 1922; UP016.001.002.001 (Box Volume 2, Box Shared 10)
    This book was published by the Tufts College Bookstore (not the Ivy Society) but the Ivy Society assisted in initial distribution of the song book.
  - Tufts Songs, 1895; UP016.001.003.001 (Box 3)
  - Tufts Songs, 1915; UP016.001.004.001 (Box Volume 4)
  - Tufts Songs, Supplement Number One, 1915; UP016.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
- The Ivy Book, 1902 -- 1977; 1902 -- 1974; UP016.002; 2.2 Linear Feet
  The Ivy book was the Tufts University student handbook until 1977 when it was replaced by the Pachyderm. The Ivy Society published the handbook until the issue for 1970/71, thereafter the university appears to have published the remaining volumes.
  - The Ivy Book, 1902 -- 1906; UP016.002.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1906 -- 1908; UP016.002.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1908 -- 1910; UP016.002.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1910 -- 1912; UP016.002.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1912 -- 1914; UP016.002.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1914 -- 1916; UP016.002.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1916 -- 1918; UP016.002.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1919 -- 1921; UP016.002.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1921 -- 1923; UP016.002.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1924 -- 1926; UP016.002.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1926 -- 1928; UP016.002.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1928 -- 1930; UP016.002.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1930 -- 1932; UP016.002.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1932 -- 1934; UP016.002.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1934 -- 1936; UP016.002.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1936 -- 1938; UP016.002.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1938 -- 1940; UP016.002.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1940 -- 1942; UP016.002.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1942 -- 1946; UP016.002.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1946 -- 1948; UP016.002.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1948 -- 1950; UP016.002.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1950 -- 1952; UP016.002.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1952 -- 1954; UP016.002.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1954 -- 1956; UP016.002.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1956 -- 1958; UP016.002.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1958 -- 1960; UP016.002.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - The Ivy Book, 1960 -- 1961; UP016.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - The Ivy Book, 1961 -- 1962; UP016.002.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - The Ivy Book, 1962 -- 1963; UP016.002.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - The Ivy Book, 1963 -- 1964; UP016.002.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - The Ivy Book, 1964 -- 1965; UP016.002.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - The Ivy Book, 1965 -- 1966; UP016.002.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - The Ivy Book, 1966 -- 1967; UP016.002.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - The Ivy Book, 1967 -- 1968; UP016.002.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - The Ivy Book, 1968 -- 1969; UP016.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - The Ivy Book, 1969 -- 1970; UP016.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - The Ivy Book, 1970 -- 1971; UP016.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - The Ivy Book, 1973 -- 1974; UP016.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - The Ivy Book, 1974 -- 1975; UP016.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - The Ivy Book, 1975 -- 1976; UP016.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - The Ivy Book, 1976 -- 1977; UP016.002.003.00007 (Box 3)